[
    {
        "front": "ا",
        "back": "alif (a as in bad or A as in fAther)"
    },
    {
        "front": "ب",
        "back": "baa'"
    },
    {
        "front": "ت",
        "back": "taa'"
    },
    {
        "front": "ث",
        "back": "thaa'"
    },
    {
        "front": "ج",
        "back": "jeem"
    },
    {
        "front": "ح",
        "back": "Haa'"
    },
    {
        "front": "خ",
        "back": "khAA' (like the ch in music composer bach)"
    },
    {
        "front": "د",
        "back": "daal"
    },
    {
        "front": "ذ",
        "back": "dhaal"
    },
    {
        "front": "ر",
        "back": "rAA"
    },
    {
        "front": "ز",
        "back": "zaee"
    },
    {
        "front": "س",
        "back": "seen"
    },
    {
        "front": "ش",
        "back": "sheen"
    },
    {
        "front": "ص",
        "back": "SAAd"
    },
    {
        "front": "ض",
        "back": "DAAd"
    },
    {
        "front": "ط",
        "back": "TAA"
    },
    {
        "front": "ظ",
        "back": "DhAA"
    },
    {
        "front": "ع",
        "back": "'ain"
    },
    {
        "front": "غ",
        "back": "ghain"
    },
    {
        "front": "ف",
        "back": "faa'"
    },
    {
        "front": "ق",
        "back": "qAAf"
    },
    {
        "front": "ك",
        "back": "kaaf"
    },
    {
        "front": "ل",
        "back": "laam"
    },
    {
        "front": "م",
        "back": "meem"
    },
    {
        "front": "ن",
        "back": "noon"
    },
    {
        "front": "ه",
        "back": "haa'"
    },
    {
        "front": "و",
        "back": "waaw"
    },
    {
        "front": "ي",
        "back": "yaa'"
    },
    {
        "front": "ء",
        "back": "hamza (glottal stop as in the - in uh-oh; we denote this as ')"
    }
]
